<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:background="@drawable/cornerless"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".TermCondition">

    <androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:fillViewport="true"
        tools:layout_editor_absoluteX="-78dp"
        tools:layout_editor_absoluteY="-168dp">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView4"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:text="Terms and Conditions"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:textSize="18sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView7"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:paddingLeft="15dp"
                android:paddingRight="15dp"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="If you create an account in the Mobile Application, you are responsible for maintaining the security of your account and you are fully responsible for all activities that occur under the account and any other actions taken in connection with it. We may, but have no obligation to, monitor and review new accounts before you may sign in and use our Services. Providing false contact information of any kind may result in the termination of your account. You must immediately notify us of any unauthorized uses of your account or any other breaches of security. We will not be liable for any acts or omissions by you, including any damages of any kind incurred as a result of such acts or omissions." />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView6"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:text="Accounts and Membership"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:textSize="18sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView5"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:paddingLeft="15dp"
                android:paddingRight="15dp"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text='These terms and conditions ("Terms", "Agreement") are an agreement between Mobile Application Developer ("Mobile Application Developer", "us", "we" or "our") and you ("User", "you" or "your"). This Agreement sets forth the general terms and conditions of your use of the Covid Tracer mobile application and any of its products or services (collectively, "Mobile Application" or "Services").' />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView8"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:gravity="center"
                android:text="Links to other mobile applications"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:textSize="18sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView9"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:paddingLeft="15dp"
                android:paddingRight="15dp"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text='Although this Mobile Application may link to other mobile applications, we are not, directly or indirectly, implying any approval, association, sponsorship, endorsement, or affiliation with any linked mobile application, unless specifically stated herein. Some of the links in the Mobile Application may be "affiliate links". This means if you click on the link and purchase an item, Mobile Application Developer will receive an affiliate commission. We are not responsible for examining or evaluating, and we do not warrant the offerings of, any businesses or individuals or the content of their mobile applications. We do not assume any responsibility or liability for the actions, products, services, and content of any other third parties. You should carefully review the legal statements and other conditions of use of any mobile application which you access through a link from this Mobile Application. Your linking to any other off-site mobile applications is at your own risk.' />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView10"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:gravity="center"
                android:text="Prohibited uses"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:textSize="18sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView11"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:paddingLeft="15dp"
                android:paddingRight="15dp"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="In addition to other terms as set forth in the Agreement, you are prohibited from using the Mobile Application or its Content: (a) for any unlawful purpose; (b) to solicit others to perform or participate in any unlawful acts; (c) to violate any international, federal, provincial or state regulations, rules, laws, or local ordinances; (d) to infringe upon or violate our intellectual property rights or the intellectual property rights of others; (e) to harass, abuse, insult, harm, defame, slander, disparage, intimidate, or discriminate based on gender, sexual orientation, religion, ethnicity, race, age, national origin, or disability; (f) to submit false or misleading information; (g) to upload or transmit viruses or any other type of malicious code that will or may be used in any way that will affect the functionality or operation of the Service or of any related mobile application, other mobile applications, or the Internet; (h) to spam, phish, pharm, pretext, spider, crawl, or scrape; (i) for any obscene or immoral purpose; or (j) to interfere with or circumvent the security features of the Service or any related mobile application, other mobile applications, or the Internet. We reserve the right to terminate your use of the Service or any related mobile application for violating any of the prohibited uses." />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView12"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:gravity="center"
                android:text="Intellectual property rights"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:textSize="18sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView13"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:paddingLeft="15dp"
                android:paddingRight="15dp"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text='"Intellectual Property Rights" means all present and future rights conferred by statute, common law or equity in or in relation to any copyright and related rights, trademarks, designs, patents, inventions, goodwill and the right to sue for passing off, rights to inventions, rights to use, and all other intellectual property rights, in each case whether registered or unregistered and including all applications and rights to apply for and be granted, rights to claim priority from, such rights and all similar or equivalent rights or forms of protection and any other results of intellectual activity which subsist or will subsist now or in the future in any part of the world. This Agreement does not transfer to you any intellectual property owned by Mobile Application Developer or third parties, and all rights, titles, and interests in and to such property will remain (as between the parties) solely with Mobile Application Developer. All trademarks, service marks, graphics and logos used in connection with the Mobile Application or Services, are trademarks or registered trademarks of Mobile Application Developer or Mobile Application Developer licensors. Other trademarks, service marks, graphics and logos used in connection with the Mobile Application or Services may be the trademarks of other third parties. Your use of the Mobile Application and Services grants you no right or license to reproduce or otherwise use any Mobile Application Developer or third party trademarks.' />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView15"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:gravity="center"
                android:text="Limitation of liability"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:textSize="18sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView14"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:paddingLeft="15dp"
                android:paddingRight="15dp"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, in no event will Mobile Application Developer, its affiliates, directors, officers, employees, agents, suppliers or licensors be liable to any person for any indirect, incidental, special, punitive, cover or consequential damages (including, without limitation, damages for lost profits, revenue, sales, goodwill, use of content, impact on business, business interruption, loss of anticipated savings, loss of business opportunity) however caused, under any theory of liability, including, without limitation, contract, tort, warranty, breach of statutory duty, negligence or otherwise, even if the liable party has been advised as to the possibility of such damages or could have foreseen such damages. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, the aggregate liability of Mobile Application Developer and its affiliates, officers, employees, agents, suppliers and licensors relating to the services will be limited to an amount greater of one dollar or any amounts actually paid in cash by you to Mobile Application Developer for the prior one month period prior to the first event or occurrence giving rise to such liability. The limitations and exclusions also apply if this remedy does not fully compensate you for any losses or fails of its essential purpose." />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView16"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:gravity="center"
                android:text="Indemnification"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:textSize="18sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView17"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:paddingLeft="15dp"
                android:paddingRight="15dp"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="You agree to indemnify and hold Mobile Application Developer and its affiliates, directors, officers, employees, agents, suppliers and licensors harmless from and against any liabilities, losses, damages or costs, including reasonable attorneys' fees, incurred in connection with or arising from any third party allegations, claims, actions, disputes, or demands asserted against any of them as a result of or relating to your Content, your use of the Mobile Application or Services or any willful misconduct on your part." />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView18"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:gravity="center"
                android:text="Severability"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:textSize="18sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView19"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:paddingLeft="15dp"
                android:paddingRight="15dp"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="All rights and restrictions contained in this Agreement may be exercised and shall be applicable and binding only to the extent that they do not violate any applicable laws and are intended to be limited to the extent necessary so that they will not render this Agreement illegal, invalid or unenforceable. If any provision or portion of any provision of this Agreement shall be held to be illegal, invalid or unenforceable by a court of competent jurisdiction, it is the intention of the parties that the remaining provisions or portions thereof shall constitute their agreement with respect to the subject matter hereof, and all such remaining provisions or portions thereof shall remain in full force and effect." />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView20"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:gravity="center"
                android:text="Dispute resolution"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:textSize="18sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView21"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:paddingLeft="15dp"
                android:paddingRight="15dp"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="The formation, interpretation, and performance of this Agreement and any disputes arising out of it shall be governed by the substantive and procedural laws of New Zealand without regard to its rules on conflicts or choice of law and, to the extent applicable, the laws of New Zealand. The exclusive jurisdiction and venue for actions related to the subject matter hereof shall be the courts located in New Zealand, and you hereby submit to the personal jurisdiction of such courts. You hereby waive any right to a jury trial in any proceeding arising out of or related to this Agreement. The United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods does not apply to this Agreement." />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView23"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:gravity="center"
                android:text="Changes and amendments"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:textSize="18sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView22"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:paddingLeft="15dp"
                android:paddingRight="15dp"
                android:gravity="center"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="We reserve the right to modify this Agreement or its policies relating to the Mobile Application or Services at any time, effective upon posting of an updated version of this Agreement in the Mobile Application. When we do, we will post a notification in our Mobile Application. Continued use of the Mobile Application after any such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes. Policy was created with WebsitePolicies." />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView24"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:gravity="center"
                android:text="Acceptance of these terms"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:textSize="18sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView25"
                android:textColor="@color/color_white"
                android:paddingLeft="15dp"
                android:paddingRight="15dp"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:layout_margin="5dp"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="You acknowledge that you have read this Agreement and agree to all its terms and conditions. By using the Mobile Application or its Services you agree to be bound by this Agreement. If you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Agreement, you are not authorized to use or access the Mobile Application and its Services." />

        </LinearLayout>
    </androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView>

</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>